newarticles.us 2013-05-24

# NewArticles.Us: new articles, free article submission, article directory

## PRIVACY POLICY

### Introduction

We at NewArticles.us are carrying on business as Article Directory Owner and we are committed to protecting any data that we collect concerning you. By using our services you agree to the use of the data that we collect in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

### We are committed to protecting your privacy

We collect the minimum amount of information about you that is commensurate with providing you with a satisfactory service. This Policy indicates the type of processes that may result in data being collected about you. Your use of this website gives us the right to collect that information. 

### Information Collected

We may collect any or all of the information that you give us depending on the type of transaction you enter into, including your name, address, telephone number, fax number and email address, together with data about your use of the website. Other information that may be needed from time to time to process a request may also be collected as indicated on the website. 

### Information Use

We use the information collected primarily to process the task for which you visited the website. Data collected is held in accordance with the Data Protection Act. All reasonable precautions are taken to prevent unauthorized access to this information. This safeguard may require you to provide additional forms of identity should you wish to obtain information about your account details. 

### Cookies 

Your Internet browser has the in-built facility for storing small files - "cookies" - that hold information which allows a website to recognise your account. Our website takes advantage of this facility to enhance your experience. You have the ability to prevent your computer from accepting cookies but, if you do, certain functionality on the website may be impaired. 

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Newarticles.us.  
Google use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Newarticles.us and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html   
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .... Google Adsense   
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.Newarticles.us send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.   
Newarticles.us has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.   
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.Newarticles.us's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.   
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

### Disclosing Information

We do not disclose any personal information obtained about you from this website to third parties except when we need to do so in order to complete the transaction - e.g. when arranging for a courier company to deliver goods that you have ordered. We may also use the information to keep in contact with you and inform you of developments associated with our business. You will be given the opportunity to remove yourself from any mailing list or similar device. If at any time in the future we should wish to disclose information collected on this website to any third party, it would only be with your knowledge and consent. 

We may from time to time provide information of a general nature to third parties - for example, the number of individuals visiting our website or completing a registration form, but we will not use any information that could identify those individuals. 

### Changes to this Policy

Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be placed here and will supersede this version of our Policy. We will take reasonable steps to draw your attention to any changes in our Policy. However, to be on the safe side, we suggest that you read this document each time you use the website to ensure that it still meets with your approval. 

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or if you want to know what information we have collected about you, please email us at info@NewArticles.us. You can also correct any factual errors in that information or require us to remove your details form any list under our control.
